export const quizQuestions_15 = {
    questions: [
      {
        question: "How many dynamic states do hyperlinks have?",
        choices: [
          "3", "4", "5", "6"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "3",
      },
      {
        question: "Which character is used between the 'a' selector and the pseudo-class name in CSS?",
        choices: [ ".", ":", "::", "-"],
        correctAnswer: ":",
      },
      {
        question: "Which of the following CSS properties controls the presence of underlines in hyperlinks?",
        choices: [  
          "text-underline",
          "text-decoration",
          "text-style",
          "text-line"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "text-decoration",
      },
      {
        question: "Which CSS property sets the distance between the text and the underline?",
        choices: [
          "text-decoration-gap",
          "underline-offset",
          "text-underline-offset",
          "text-decoration-spacing"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "text-underline-offset",
      },
      {
        question: "Which CSS property would you use to create a smooth transition between hyperlink states?",
        choices: [
          "animation",
          "transform",
          "transition",
          "ease"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "transition",
      },
      {
        question: "Which of the following are considered 'passive' hyperlink states?",
        choices: [       
          "hover and active",
          "link and visited",
          "focus and hover",
          "active and focus"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "link and visited",
      },
      {
        question: "Where would you typically remove underlines from hyperlinks?",
        choices: [      
          "In paragraphs",
          "In headings",
          "In navigation menus and footers",
          "In all hyperlinks"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "In navigation menus and footers",
      },
      {
        question: "Which CSS property sets the thickness of the underline in hyperlinks?",
        choices: [        
          "text-decoration-width",
          "text-decoration-size",
          "text-decoration-thickness",
          "text-underline-thickness"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "text-decoration-thickness",
      },
      {
        question: "What is the main purpose of changing hyperlink styles based on their state?",
        choices: [  
          "To make the webpage more colorful",
          "To provide clear visual feedback to users",
          "To demonstrate CSS skills",
          "To follow web standards"],
        correctAnswer: "To provide clear visual feedback to users",
      },

      {
        question: "Which pseudo-class targets a hyperlink while it's being clicked?",
        choices: [ 
          "a:clicked",
          "a:active",
          "a:pressed",
          "a:down"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "a:active",
      },
    ],
  };
  